var questions = [
    {
        question: 'Is Harry a muggle?',
        choices: [
            'True',
            'False',
        ],
        correct: 1,
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is a slytherin?',
        choices: [
            'Harry',
            'Luna',
            'Ron',
            'Malfoy',
        ],
        correct: 3,
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the Hogwarts founders created the Chamber of Secrets?',
        choices: [
            'Neville Longbottom',
            'Rowena Ravenclaw',
            'Salazar Slytherin',
            'Zacharias Smith'
        ],
        correct: 2,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the name of Harry Potter\'s owl?',
        choices: [
            'Hedwig',
            'Errol',
            'Crookshanks',
            'Dobby'
        ],
        correct: 0,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the street address of the Dursley home? ',
        choices: [
            '12 Grimmauld Place ',
            ' 4 Privet Drive',
            ' 3 Little Hangleton',
            '5 Godric\'s Hollow'
        ],
        correct: 1,
    },
    {
        question: 'What Animagus form is taken by Sirius Black?',
        choices: [
            'Stag',
            'Dog',
            'Werewolf',
            'Hippogriff'
        ],
        correct: 1,
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these spells is used to unlock doors? ',
        choices: [
            'Avada Cadavra',
            'Abra Cadabra',
            'Alohamora',
            'Leviosa'
        ],
        correct: 2,
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these objects is not a component of the Deathly Hallows?',
        choices: [
            'Elder Wand',
            'Invisibility cloak',
            'Sorcerer\'s Stone',
            'Resurrection Stone?'
        ],
        correct: 2,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the form of Hermione\'s patronus?',
        choices: [
            'Doe',
            'Stag',
            'Rabbit',
            'Otter'
        ],
        correct: 3,
    },
    {
        question: 'When is Harrys birthday',
        choices: [
            'July 31',
            'August 25',
            'June 30',
            'July 15'
        ],
        correct: 0,
    }
]
